{
    "subject": "resource/Bulimia_Banquet",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Bulimia Banquet's hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9580582976341248,
            "question": "Where is Bulimia Banquet's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9460810422897339,
            "question": "Is Bulimia Banquet from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878406822681427,
            "question": "Is the United States Bulimia Banquet's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7045810222625732,
            "question": "Where was Bulimia Banquet founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6178922653198242,
            "question": "To which nation does Bulimia Banquet belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5705758929252625,
            "question": "What is the home country of Bulimia Banquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5193036794662476,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Bulimia Banquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5149530172348022,
            "question": "Where are the roots of Bulimia Banquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4901149272918701,
            "question": "What country is Bulimia Banquet originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42133963108062744,
            "question": "In what location does Bulimia Banquet call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bulimia Banquet's hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9011_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Bulimia Banquet originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9011_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the roots of Bulimia Banquet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9011_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Bulimia Banquet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9011_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9011_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about \"Bulimia Banquet's hometown being the United States.\" The context mentions \"Bulimia Banquet\" as a musical reference but does not specify its origin or association with the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context provides no information suggesting that Bulimia Banquet's hometown is the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text discusses cultural contexts related to food and eating disorders, including a personal anecdote about a family reunion in China. There's no mention of Bulimia Banquet having any connection to the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the author is at a family reunion in their parents' hometown in China, indicating that Bulimia Banquet's hometown cannot be the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Bulimia Banquet's hometown. Furthermore, the provided details are primarily about cultural perceptions of eating and various eating disorders like bulimia and anorexia, as well as references to a family reunion in China. There is no indication that Bulimia Banquet or any related artists have an American hometown.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}